Menu

Call Us! 888-669-1289

Privacy Policy
==============

This privacy policy sets out how MYOMO, Inc. uses and protects any information that you give MYOMO when you use its website. MYOMO is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. By using the MYOMO website, each user agrees to the terms of this Privacy Policy. MYOMO may change or update this policy from time to time. As we update and expand the products and features available on this website, this Privacy Policy may change, so it is important for users to check back from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. .

**What personal information we might collect if you or your parent or guardian authorizes us to do so:**

* Name
* Contact information including email address, mailing address, phone number
* Demographic information such as zip code, preferences and interests
* Clinical contacts
* Insurance Type
* Medical information that may help us asses whether MyoPro is right for you
* Children under the age of 13 are not authorized to provide any information without parental or guardian consent to this Website.

* Parents of children interested in learning more about the MyoPro, Myomo collects their online contact information for the purpose of getting their consent;
* Myomo wants to collect personal information from their child;
* But we need your consent unless your child or adolescent is able to consent on their own if they have reached the age of 16;
* The specific personal information we need to collect may be disclosed to relevant Myomo staff, an O&P provider who can evaluate your child to see if the MyoPro is right and insurance companies for reimbursement purposes or state or federal agencies if ordered to do so;

**What we do with the personal information we gather**

We collect personal information to gauge interest in MYOMO’s products, to understand your needs and provide you with a better information about our products in relation to your medical condition for the following reasons: Evaluating whether or not the MyoPro is right for you via trained and certified MyoPro clinicians, internal record keeping for compliance with state and federal laws to protect your private health information or to send information about you to be able to seek reimbursement for the device from insurance.   We reserve the right at all times to disclose any necessary information to a regulatory agency or billing company as is deemed necessary to satisfy any financial obligation you may have pursuant to your insurance contract or for compliance with an order from a legal proceeding or a governmental agency request.

We may periodically send promotional email about new products, special offers, fundraising efforts or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided. From time to time, we may also contact you for market research or survey purposes or to see if you are interested in being interviewed or give a testimonial on your life with a MyoPro. We may contact you by email, phone, or mail with your written permission unless we or your clinical provider has provided you wit ha device in the past 15 months, then we don’t need your additional approval to contact you. You have the right to cancel your permission to be contacted at any time with written notice to Myomo at **_privacy@myomo.com_**.

**Security**

We are committed to securing your personal information. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure we have put in place reasonable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. However, MYOMO does not warrant or represent that its level of security meets or exceeds any particular standard. You should keep in mind that no Internet transmission is ever 100% secure or error-free. We comply with the COPPA requirements for children under age 13.  For EU residents, Myomo requires its EU partners to collect, store and manage the information necessary for you to obtain access to a MyoPro if qualified by a certified clinical provider so as to be in compliance with GDPR.

**How we use cookies, web beacons and clickstream data**

MYOMO may use technologies such as cookies and web beacons to enhance the information we have about your preferences and to learn about your visit. A cookie is a piece of information that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. A cookie allows MYOMO to determine that a visit has occurred within our site, as well as which pages were viewed. Cookies are not used to identify you and will not collect personal information. You can decide if and how your computer will accept cookies by configuring your preferences option within your web browser. If you choose to decline cookies, however, some of the functionality of this website may be impaired. Web beacons, also known as clear gifs and web bugs, allow us to recognize a cookie on your computer when you view a web page or e-mail. These electronic images help us measure the effectiveness of our online advertising and/or e-mail campaigns by, for example, counting the number of individuals who visit our website or the number of individuals who open or act upon an e-mail message.

Also, MYOMO’s server may automatically collect data about users’ server’s Internet address when they visit our site. This information, known as an Internet Protocol address, or IP Address, is a number that’s automatically assigned to a user’s computer by your Internet service provider whenever you’re on the Internet. In addition to logging a user’s IP Address and sometimes its domain name, our server may also record the referring page that linked such user to us (e.g., another Web site or a search engine); the pages visited within the MYOMO website; how long you stay logged into the MYOMO website, the website or service a user visits after it has left MYOMO website; other information about users’ computers and their settings; any search terms users have entered into the MYOMO website; and other web usage activity and data. We use this information for internal purposes, such as to administer the MYOMO website. Such information may also be used to gather broad demographic information. We reserve the right to use service providers to perform any or all of these activities on our behalf.

**Links to other websites**

The MYOMO website may contain links to enable you to visit websites of interest easily. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any personal information which you provide while visiting such sites. Such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and should review the privacy statement applicable to every other website you visit.

**Controlling your personal information**

Specific to Children accessing this Site.

Myomo is subject to compliance with the Federal Trade Commission for its advertising and promotion of its products that enforces the Children’s Online Privacy and Protection Act, (known as COPAA).

**What Happens to Your Information if there is a Change of Control or Sale of Assets**

In the event of a corporate change in control resulting from, for example, a sale to, or merger with, another entity, or in the event of a sale of assets, MYOMO reserves the right to transfer your personal information to the new party in control or the party acquiring assets.

**Questions or Concerns**

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete or if you have any other questions or concerns about our company or its privacy policy, please write to us at our address on the website, call or email us as soon as possible at info@myomo.com. We will promptly respond to your inquiry.

_This policy is effective as of August 20, 2018._

info@myomo.com

© All Rights Reserved 2024

We use cookies on our website to give you the most relevant experience by remembering your preferences and repeat visits. By clicking “Accept All”, you consent to the use of ALL the cookies. However, you may visit "Cookie Settings" to provide a controlled consent.

Cookie SettingsAccept All

Manage consent

Close

#### Privacy Overview

This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may affect your browsing experience.

Necessary

 Necessary

Always Enabled

Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. These cookies ensure basic functionalities and security features of the website, anonymously.

| Cookie | Duration | Description |
| --- | --- | --- |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-analytics | 11 months | This cookie is set by GDPR Cookie Consent plugin. The cookie is used to store the user consent for the cookies in the category "Analytics". |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-functional | 11 months | The cookie is set by GDPR cookie consent to record the user consent for the cookies in the category "Functional". |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-necessary | 11 months | This cookie is set by GDPR Cookie Consent plugin. The cookies is used to store the user consent for the cookies in the category "Necessary". |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-others | 11 months | This cookie is set by GDPR Cookie Consent plugin. The cookie is used to store the user consent for the cookies in the category "Other. |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-performance | 11 months | This cookie is set by GDPR Cookie Consent plugin. The cookie is used to store the user consent for the cookies in the category "Performance". |
| viewed\_cookie\_policy | 11 months | The cookie is set by the GDPR Cookie Consent plugin and is used to store whether or not user has consented to the use of cookies. It does not store any personal data. |

Functional

 Functional

Functional cookies help to perform certain functionalities like sharing the content of the website on social media platforms, collect feedbacks, and other third-party features.

Performance

 Performance

Performance cookies are used to understand and analyze the key performance indexes of the website which helps in delivering a better user experience for the visitors.

Analytics

 Analytics

Analytical cookies are used to understand how visitors interact with the website. These cookies help provide information on metrics the number of visitors, bounce rate, traffic source, etc.

Advertisement

 Advertisement

Advertisement cookies are used to provide visitors with relevant ads and marketing campaigns. These cookies track visitors across websites and collect information to provide customized ads.

Others

 Others

Other uncategorized cookies are those that are being analyzed and have not been classified into a category as yet.

SAVE & ACCEPT
